idroo.com 2017-02-12

# IDroo | Privacy Policy

Last modified: November 15, 2013

There are different ways you can use our services – to communicate and collaborate with other people, share or to create new content. To use some of our services you may need to share information with us, for example by creating an IDroo Account. As you use our services, we want you to be clear how we're using information and the ways in which you can protect your privacy.

## Our Privacy Policy explains:

  * What information we collect and why we collect it.
  * How we use that information.
  * The choices we offer, including how to access and update information.

## Key terms

  *  **Cookie**

A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies.

  *  **IDroo Account**

You may access some of our services by signing up for an IDroo Account and providing us with some personal information (typically your name, email address and a password). This account information will be used to authenticate you when you access our services and protect your account from unauthorized access by others. You can edit or terminate your account at any time through your IDroo Account settings.

  *  **IP address**

Every computer connected to the Internet is assigned a unique number known as an Internet protocol (IP) address.

  *  **Personal information**

This is information which you provide to us which personally identifies you, such as your name, email address.

## Information we collect

We collect information to provide better services to all of our users.

We collect information in two ways:

  * **Information you give us.**

For example, when you sign up for an IDroo Account we'll ask for personal information, like your name or email address. You may also add personal information like name of photo to your profile.

  *  **Information we get from your use of our services.**

We may collect information about the services that you use and how you use them. This information includes:

    *  **Device information**

We may collect device-specific information

    *  **Log information**

When you use our services or view content provided by Iteral Group, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include:

      * details of how you used our service.
      * Internet protocol address.
      * device event information such as browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.
      * cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your IDroo Account.
    *  **Cookies**

We use cookies to help manage your session on the site.

## How we use information we collect

We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to protect Iteral Group and our users.

When you contact Iteral Group, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing. We may use your email address to inform you about our services, such as letting you know about upcoming changes or improvements.

We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Privacy Policy.

Iteral Group processes personal information on our servers. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country where you live.

## Transparency and choice

People have different privacy concerns. Our goal is to be clear about what information we collect, so that you can make meaningful choices about how it is used.

You set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us. However, it's important to remember that our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

## Information you share

Our services may let you share information with others. Remember that when you share information publicly, it may be indexable by search engines. Our services provide you with different options on sharing and removing your content.

## Accessing and updating your personal information

Whenever you use our services, we aim to provide you with access to your personal information. If that information is wrong, we strive to give you ways to update it quickly or to delete it – unless we have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes. When updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request.

We may reject requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort (for example, developing a new system or fundamentally changing an existing practice), risk the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes).

Where we can provide information access and correction, we will do so for free, except where it would require a disproportionate effort. We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our services, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and may not remove information from our backup systems.

## Information we share

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of Iteral Group unless one of the following circumstances apply:

  *  **With your consent**

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Iteral Group when we have your consent to do so.

  *  **For external processing**

We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

  *  **For legal reasons**

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Iteral Group if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:

    * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
    * enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.
    * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
    * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Iteral Group, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If Iteral Group is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Information security

We work hard to protect Iteral Group and our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold.

## Application

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by Iteral Group OÜ.

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including content that may be displayed to you by other sites linked from our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.

## Changes

Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes).
